Information

Disclaimer
"The Settlers IV Enhanced Edition" is a user created modification. The installation changes original files of "The Settlers IV". These changes may only be removed by a new installation of the program or by restoring the previously saved files. The installation is at your own risk. Neither the creator of this modification, nor the creator of the installation program, nor the distributor of this software can be held liable in any way for possible damages to the system or other programs.

Copyright
All graphics and text content, as well as all other information in this application, are copyrighted by Blue Byte, Ubisoft or the creators of this modification. These may not be copied or used in extracts without permission of the respective author. Registered trademarks are not separately marked as such.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Informationen

Disclaimer
"The Settlers IV Enhanced Edition" ist eine von Usern erstellte Modifikation. Durch die Installation werden Originaldateien von "The Settlers IV" verändert. Diese Veränderungen lassen sich unter Umständen nur durch eine Neuinstallation des Programms oder durch ein Zurückspielen der vorher gesicherten Dateien wieder beseitigen. Die Installation erfolgt ausschließlich auf eigenes Risiko. Weder der Ersteller dieser Modifikation, noch der Ersteller des Installationsprogramms, noch der Vertreiber dieser Software können wegen eventuell entstandener Schäden am System oder an anderen Programmen in irgendeiner Weise haftbar gemacht werden.

Copyright
Sämtliche Grafiken und Textinhalte, sowie alle anderen Informationen dieser Anwendung, unterliegen dem Copyright von Blue Byte, Ubisoft oder den Erstellern dieser Modifikation. Diese dürfen ohne Genehmigung des jeweiligen Autors weder kopiert, noch auszugsweise weiterverwendet werden. Eingetragene Marken sind nicht gesondert als solche gekennzeichnet.
